

Contact

- Cracow
- +48 668 548 773
- macieknecka@gmail.com
- <u>GitHub</u>
- <u>LinkedIn</u>
- Portfolio

Technical skills

- React
- Redux
- React Styled
 JavaScript
- - Components JavaScript API
- React Router HTML
- CSS
- RWD
- Sass
- GitHub
- Jest
- Git
- ISON
- Babel
- BEM
- REST API
- Webpack
- VS Code
- Npm

Soft skills

- Problem solving
- Creativity
- Independence
- Commitment
- High personal culture
- Communication skills

Maciej Nęcka

Front-end developer

I am an enthusiastic front-end developer who has been continuously expanding knowledge and skills in the fascinating world of user interface creation. I have been learning programming for 1.5 year and plan on changing the profession. My passions include coding, technological innovations, and the world of MMORPG games.

Projects

Portfolio Website

I invite you to explore my portfolio website, which has been created with passion and great attention to detail. The site serves as a showcase of my projects and professional achievements. All elements of the portfolio have been designed with the aim of providing intuitive navigation and a user-friendly experience, allowing for easy and quick access to information of interest.

GitHub - Portfolio Website

Live – Portfolio Website

Meeting Form

An application built using React that serves the purpose of managing meetings. It assists users in organizing and tracking their meetings.

GitHub – Meeting form

Live demo – Meeting form

Tasks manager

A simple React application for effective task management. It allows users to add, start/stop, complete, and delete tasks. The application also tracks the time dedicated to each task.

GitHub – Task manager

Live demo – Task manager

AppLab RWD

A modern, responsive website template. It includes various sections such as a navigation menu, header, main features, pricing, and customer reviews. The primary goal of this project was to use only HTML and CSS to create a responsive design.

GitHub – AppLab

<u>Live demo – AppLab</u>

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the European Parliament's and Council of the European Union Regulation on the Protection of Natural Persons as of 27 April 2016, with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC.

Hobbies

- Artificial Intelligence
- Technological innovations
- MMORPG games

Languages

- Polish native
- English B2/C1

Education

2023-currently

DevMentor.pl

Individual mentoring with <u>Mateusz Bogolubow</u>: 6-month course preparing for a Front-end developer position.

Material scope:

- HTML i CSS
- RWD (Responsive Web Design)
- REST API
- Jest
- React
- Redux
- Styled Components
- React Testing Library
- CI/CD

2012-2016

Economic School Complex No.1

Certification:

• Economic Technician

Work Experience

2020-currently

Proton Marek Król

Sales Specialist

- Sales data analysis
- Collaboration with IT department
- Carying of fundamental data security
- Order placement, receiving deliveries, and quality control of received products
- POS/BOS systems handling
- Communication skills
- Providing High-Quality customer service

2016-2020

DE NOVO II

Window Film Installer

- Organization and project management
- Communication skills
- Technical skills
- Attention to detail and precision
- Ensuring professional customer service
- Installation of various types of window films
- Utilization of specialized technologies and tools

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the European Parliament's and Council of the European Union Regulation on the Protection of Natural Persons as of 27 April 2016, with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC.